# **Christopher Ogbonnaya**

With a background in **bartending, serving, and customer service**, I am equipped with the ability to thrive in a demanding environment while delivering top-notch service to patrons. With a friendly demeanour, excellent communication skills, and a keen eye for detail, I am committed to ensuring guest satisfaction and exceeding expectations. I also possess fundamental understanding in computing and programming, having experience coding in Java, Python, and HTML.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Chicken Republic, Lagos, Nigeria — Cashier

October 2021 - January 2022

- In charge of cashiering, customer service, and returns.
- Managed customer satisfaction
- Gained expertise in-store security.

# **The Wave Church,** Winnipeg, Canada — Volunteering

April 2022 - May 2022

- Prepared for events by setting up tables and chairs and unloading equipment.
- Chop fruits and vegetables to distribute to people.
- Raised funds for the organization through community outreach initiatives.

### **RBC Convention Centre**, Winnipeg, Canada — Banquet Server

August 2022 - Present day

- Experience serving food and drinks.
- Assisting with setup of the event space and cleanup after the event is finished.
- Bartending and customer service experience.
- Sophistication in table preparation

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Winnipeg**, Winnipeg — BSc. Computer Science

May 2022 - Present

- Member of the UWACSSA for computer science
- Over twenty credits in computer science related courses

Arc-En-Ciel International High School, Lomé - TOGO - High School Diploma

### September 2014 - June 2021

- Class President
- Member of multiple school-affiliated clubs
- Studied in a French environment.
- Studied in an International Baccalaureate Program

# **SKILLS**

- Cheerful Outlook
- Organized and Efficient
- Bilingual (English and French fluently)
- Relationship Building
- Friendly and Outgoing
- Resolute Diligent worker.
- Coding and programming knowledge